livecellresearch.com 2017-06-24

# Live Cell Research | Privacy Policy

Please review this Privacy Policy carefully. We value your privacy and appreciate the importance of your trust and have set forth this Privacy Policy and Cookies Notice to explain how Living Cell Research, LLC d/b/a Live Cell Research™ (hereafter, "Live Cell Research™", "we", "us", or "our") collect, protect, and use your information as part of our technology platforms, including, without limitation, our company websites, web pages, sponsored social media platforms, mobile sites, and mobile apps.

Your use of this Website constitutes your acceptance of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with the Privacy Policy, then you do not have the right to access, view, download or otherwise use this Website or purchase any product and, accordingly, you should not do so.

You may visit or browser this Website without providing identifiable information about yourself. However, this may limit your ability to receive certain features, products, or services from Live Cell Research™.

#### Information We Collect

### Information You May Provide:

We may collect Personal information, information that can be used to identify you as an individual, such as your name, email, telephone number, home address, demographic information, or payment information, such as account or card number, when you make your purchase. The type of personal information we may collect depends on your use of this Website. If you register on this Website, enter a promotion, make a purchase, opt-in to receive emails or other offers and communications, we collect and store that information provided. We may ask you to provide other information, such as demographic information, or opinion and/or statement pertaining to the Product. 

### Information We Collect Automatically:

Site Usage Information: Live Cell Research™ and its third-party service providers, such as Google Analytics™, may also use a variety of technologies that passively or automatically collect information about how this Website accesses and uses ("Usage Information"), including your browser type, device type, operating system, application version, the pages served to you, the time you browser, preceding page views, and your use of features or applications on this Website. This statistical data helps us understand what is interesting and relevant to users of this Website so we can best adapt our content.

Device Identifiers: Live Cell Research™ also automatically collects an IP address or other unique identifier information ("identifying Information") from the computer, mobile device, technology or other device (collectively, "Device") you use to access this Website. Identifying Information is a number that is automatically assigned to your device when you access a web site or its servers, and our computers identify your device by its identifying information. We may use the identifying information to, among other things, administer this Website, help diagnose problems with our servers, analyze trends, track users’ web page movements, help identify you and your shopping cart, and gather broad demographic information for collected use.

Cookies: Live Cell Research™ uses "Cookies", which are data files placed on a device when it is used to visit this Website to facilitate site navigation and to personalize your experience, including adapting advertisements. Cookies may also be used to associate you with social networking sites like Facebook, Twitter, and Instagram and, if you so choose, enable interaction of your activities on this Website.

If you prefer not to accept cookies, you can change your browser settings to notify you when you receive cookies, which allow you to accept or reject it; or set your browser to not accept any cookies. Be aware that some features or services may not work properly if cookies are blocked.

#### Information From Third Parties

We may receive information about you form third parties that include our products or promotional offers if you opt-in to receive information from us. You may also choose to participate in a third party application or social media site through which you allow us to collect information about you, including personal information such as your name, email, telephone number, home address, demographic information, and/or payment information, such as account or card number. 

#### Use and Sharing of Information

We use the information we collect about you for the following, including:

  * Verify your Identity;
  * Fulfill your product purchases;
  * Responding to your questions;
  * Providing you access to certain areas and features of this Website
  * Communicating with you about your purchase and activities on this Website
  * Adapting content, advertisements, and offers we provide you directly or through third-party partners.
  * Improving the Website and Customer Experience
  * Sending Notice or Information

Except as provided in this Privacy Policy, we will not provide any of your personal information to third parties without your specific consent. We may share non-personal information, such as user statistics or demographics, as set forth in this agreement.

We may share your personal information with other entities and our affiliates of companies controlled by Live Cell Research™ for internal reasons, primarily for business and operational purposes.

Legal Disclosure: We may transfer and disclose information, including your Personal Information, Usage Information, and Identifying Information, including IP address, to third parties to comply with a legal obligation; at the request of governmental authorities conducting an investigation; or otherwise to protect the rights, property, safety, or security of third parties, visitors to this Website, or the public.

#### Opt-Out of Target Advertising

If you do not wish to receive targeted advertising, you can opt out. You can opt out by visiting the "Manage Subscriptions" tab at the bottom of any emailed advertisement. Your request to opt out will be processed within 10 business days. Please note that even if you remove your information (opt out), you will still see advertisements while browsing this Website or the Internet. 

#### Security and Your Information

Live Cell Research™ maintains reasonable safeguards to protect Personal Information against loss, unauthorized use, disclosure or destruction and when transferring information for processing. However, no electronic data transmission or storage of information can be 100% secure. Please note that we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information to you transmit to us.

#### California Residents

Many browsers have a "Do Not Track" feature that allows you to instruct websites that you do not want them to track your online activities. These browser features are not uniform, so we are not currently set up to respond to this feature.

California residents who have provided their personal information to us may request data regarding disclosures of their information to third parties for direct marketing purposes. Such requests may be submitted to us by email at support@LiveCellResearch.com or at the following mailing address: Attention: Live Cell Research™ Customer Service, 10866 Washington Blvd., #815, Culver City, CA 90232

Please specify in your communication that you are making a "California Shine the Light" inquiry. We will respond to your inquiry within 30 days.

#### Children's Privacy

This Site is not directed to children under the age of thirteen (13). Children may not use our services, and we do not knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of thirteen (13). We have no way of distinguishing the age of individuals who address our Site. If a child has provided us with personal information, the parent or guardian should contact us to remove the information and opt out of promotional opportunities.

#### Consent to Processing of Information

This Website is governed by and operated in, and in accordance with the laws of, the United States, and are intended for the enjoyment of residents of the United States. If you are located in the European Union, Canada or elsewhere outside of the United States, please be aware that information we collect may be transferred to and processed in the United States. By using this Website, or providing us with any information, you (a) acknowledge that this Website is subject to the laws of the United States, (b) consent to the collection, processing, maintenance and transfer of such information in and to the United States and other applicable territories in which the privacy laws may not be as comprehensive as or equivalent to those in the country where you reside and/or are a citizen, and (c) waive any claims that may arise under those laws.

#### Cookies and Other Technology:

Like many sites, our Site employs cookies, JavaScript tags and Web beacons (also known as clear GIF technology or "action tags") to speed your navigation of our Site, recognize you and your access privileges, and track your usage of our Site. Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored as text files by your Internet browser on your computer's hard drive for record keeping purposes. Most Internet browsers are initially set to accept cookies. You can set your browser to refuse cookies from Web sites or to remove cookies from your hard drive, but if you do, you will not be able to access or use portions of our Site.

We use both persistent cookies and third party cookies. We use persistent cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our Site. The persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. Third party cookies are only used for short-term tracking. You can remove the cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser's "help" file. Persistent and third party cookies also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our Site. If you reject cookies, you may still use our Site, but your ability to use some areas of our Site, such as a shopping cart, will be limited and may not function properly. You can opt-out of third party cookies by visiting [Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

#### Changes and Updates to This Policy

Please note, we may change information on this Website and/or this Privacy Policy, at any time without prior notice to you, and any changes will be effective immediately upon the posting of the revised Privacy Policy on this Website. We will use your Personal Information in a manner consistent with the Privacy Policy and in effect at the time you submitted the information, unless you consent to the new or revised policy. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

#### Contact Us

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy please contact us at:

To reach us by email:   
support@LiveCellResearch.com

To reach us by phone:   
844-650-5933

Monday - Friday 5am to 7pm PST   
Saturday - Sunday 6am to 4:30pm PST

#### Effective Date

4/13/2017
